ARIADNE E. PAREDES

ABOUT ME

Experienced EdTech Customer Success and Professional Services professional with over 10 years of experience in the educational field. I am looking to support successful rollouts at scale, effectively managing multiple partners and projects to make a positive impact over school districts nation-wide.

SKILLS

ChurnZero I Salesforce I Jira I ZenDesk I FileZilla I ShareFile I Concur I Trello I Small Improvements I Slack I Okta I Zoom I TEAMS I GSuite I MS Office I Spanish (Native) I French (Conversational).

EXPERIENCE

Partner Success Manager

April 2021 – Present

Ellevation Education, Remote

- Manage implementation, ongoing support, and customer health for 100+ accounts totalling over \$1M in TCV, maintaining high levels of satisfaction and adoption.
- Analyze key data dashboards (usage, satisfaction, data freshness), to monitor partner health and develop action plans that prevent churn and promote renewals and expansions.
- Collaborate with various teams such as Sales, Data Integration, Product, Marketing, Product Support, etc., giving feedback as needed to develop scalable solutions for partners.
- Lead working sessions that unite partners nation-wide and increase key stakeholder's capacity.
- Inform and support Leadership's effort in creating diverse, equitable, and inclusive spaces and experiences across the company by implementing key DEIB initiatives.
- Founded Ellevation's Learn@Work Committee to promote continuous learning and provide opportunities for leadership development, professional learning, and cross-team collaboration.

Training Solutions Manager

Nov. 2017 – Present

Ellevation Education, Remote

- Led online and in-person PD focused on helping new and ongoing districts effectively use Ellevation tools, maintaining a consistent post-training satisfaction average of over 95%.
- Analyzed, disaggregated, and shared training data and results to address district partner's needs, maintain engagement, and continually refine support provided.
- Communicated and collaborated closely with partners, and Success teams to verify district database accuracy, configurations, goals, and other priorities are set for training.
- Proactively monitored partner needs, law updates, and product changes that impact training through dogfooding, state-specific meetings, demo Fridays, internal notices, etc.

Multilingual Programs Specialist – Secondary Division

Aug. 2016 – Nov. 2017

Houston ISD, Houston, TX

- Analyzed data to develop informed campus action plans for the advancement of students, quality instruction, and compliance at the largest school district in Texas, Houston ISD.
- Designed and delivered specialized professional development and coaching district-wide.
- Presented at regional, state, and national conferences such as Title III Symposium, ALAS, etc.

EDUCATION

- Master's in Business Administration Louisiana State University at Shreveport
- B.A. in International Political Economy The University of Texas at Dallas
- Certifications: CompTIA CTT+ Certification; EC-6 Standard Texas Educator Certificate